<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>editing on Jexetic.com</title>
    <link>https://www.jexetic.com/tags/editing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in editing on Jexetic.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 15:11:19 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jexetic.com/tags/editing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Diary of a Caffeine Addict</title>
      <link>https://www.jexetic.com/posts/diary-of-a-caffeine-addict/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 15:11:19 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jexetic.com/posts/diary-of-a-caffeine-addict/</guid>
      <description>My G Fuel is coming today (you can make fun of me if you want, but I’m addicted to the caffeine). I didn’t have any yesterday and ended up with a wicked headache, so that was fun. I couldn’t start my day with caffeine today, so I’ve been passing the time by editing video. I made my YouTube short that’ll go up today and one to go up tomorrow. Tomorrow’s is better.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>My G Fuel is coming today (you can make fun of me if you want, but I’m addicted to the caffeine). I didn’t have any yesterday and ended up with a wicked headache, so that was fun. I couldn’t start my day with caffeine today, so I’ve been passing the time by editing video. I made my YouTube short that’ll go up today and one to go up tomorrow. Tomorrow’s is better. Today’s is good too, it’s just only eight seconds which might be a lil too short. Hopefully, the algorithm likes them.</p>
<p>Other than editing, I sent my job the official documents they needed. I’ve got another job doing a background check on me. I’m not sure if I want the new job or not. I definitely need a different job than I’ve got currently because I need more money, but the one I’m being offered would be a really long bus ride, and I’m not totally vibing with that. It’s also less pay, but that hardly matters with how few hours I get at my current job. But I dunno, I just probably need to decide by Sunday.</p>
<p>Maybe I’ll do some online shopping. I don’t really need to actually buy stuff until I get a better job, but I want to get more HomeKit stuff for when I move. I don’t want any non-HomeKit lights in my room. If whatever room I move into has non-standard bulbs like my current room does, I’m just getting more light strips/lamps and never turning them on lol. But I do like bright, warm light. I hate cool light, but I do need a lot of light to feel awake. But I think I could pull it off with enough light strips. But that’s only if I don’t end up in a room where they’ve never heard of normal light bulbs.</p>
<p>Tomorrow my desk comes. It does not come put together. That process is likely to be irritating enough that I won’t want to record it, but I’m gonna try to take some pictures along the way so I can at least post them here. And maybe on Instagram because I’m still deciding if I wanna actually use that website or not. Or&hellip; Mastodon? maybe? I need to make a whole separate post about Mastodon at some point. I wanna like it, but it also seems kinda pointless. I also signed up for the Bluesky beta, but I’ve heard it’s got moderation issues and other similar issues to Twitter. Which would be totally crazy if the Twitter clone made by the old Twitter boss had Twitter issues.</p>
<p>Speaking of social media, can we talk about how fucking dumb Redditors are? Motherfuckers just make shit up. I’ve seen two separate discussions this week about how we should’ve known Google was gonna be evil when they took “don’t be evil” out of their code of conduct. Except&hellip; that’s still there. And those words never changed the fact that they have always been a capitalist company that only exists to make money, anyway. But great observation, you dumbasses.</p>
<p>Anyway, this is just something I’m trying. I think I’ll try to make myself put something up on this site every day. Even if it’s just sort of a journal for myself to look back on later. Could be nice. I dunno.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
