<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>politics on Jexetic.com</title>
    <link>https://www.jexetic.com/tags/politics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in politics on Jexetic.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 19:18:40 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jexetic.com/tags/politics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Religion vs English</title>
      <link>https://www.jexetic.com/posts/religion-vs-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 19:18:40 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jexetic.com/posts/religion-vs-english/</guid>
      <description>Bitwarden has recently fired their vice president of software engineering in Jacksonville, Florida for listing his pronouns in Slack as “assigned by God.”
Let’s talk about that for a moment. Did God, in this case, not assign you a specific gender? When people talk about you, do they not refer to you as he or her? Your religion is against a whole chunk of the English language? Having your pronouns assigned by God doesn’t even clash with listing them in Slack.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitwarden has recently fired their vice president of software engineering in Jacksonville, Florida for listing his pronouns in Slack as “assigned by God.”</p>
<p>Let’s talk about that for a moment. Did God, in this case, not assign you a specific gender? When people talk about you, do they not refer to you as he or her? Your religion is against a whole chunk of the English language? Having your pronouns assigned by God doesn’t even clash with listing them in Slack. You firmly believe you were assigned he/him by God and that shouldn’t be changed. Fine! Literally just list those assigned pronouns. I’m quite confused about what’s difficult here.</p>
<p>Has anyone ever said “Yeah I was talking to assigned by God today and assigned by God is really having a rough time with assigned by God’s inability to do basic tasks.” Oh, they haven’t? Because your pronouns are he/him? And “assigned by God” isn’t a pronoun? Weird.</p>
<p>If you aren&rsquo;t using a password manager, you should be, and I highly recommend Bitwarden :)</p>
<p><em>Edited 6/18/23 to fix a typo, clarify a bit, and change title</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
